# Curriculum Vitae

My name is Samuele.

I'm an Italian spatial data scientist passionate about GIS & programming.

Currently, I work at Eurac Research on climate-neutral territories.

The best way to get a hold of me is via email: <a href="mailto:samuelezilio95@gmail.com">samuelezilio95@gmail.com</a>.

You can also find me on GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/samuzilio">https://github.com/samuzilio</a>.

## Work Experience

06/2024 - Ongoing

Researcher

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

05/2021 - 05/2024

**Junior Researcher** 

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

09/2020 - 04/2021

**Trainee** 

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

### Education

2017 - 2020

#### **MSc in Urban and Regional Planning**

IUAV, Venice (Italy) + Universidade de Lisboa, Lisbon (Portugal)

2014 - 2017

#### **BSc in Urban and Regional Planning**

IUAV, Venice (Italy) + İstanbul Teknik Üniversitesi, Istanbul (Turkey)